(Sheldon:)-Sarcasm?
-Yes.
(Howard:)But mixed with genuine concern.
(Sheldon:)For your information...
(Sheldon:)...I'll be playing host
to Dr. Elizabeth Plimpton.
(Raj:)-Cosmological physicist from Princeton?
-Yes.
(Sheldon:)And until you acquire
a surgical mask...
(Sheldon:)...please address your comments to me
through a napkin.
(Sheldon:)We've been corresponding for years
about our mutual interest...
(Sheldon:)...in gravitational wave signatures
of inflatons in the early universe.
(Sheldon:)Now she's under consideration
for a position at our university.
(Leonard:)Why didn't you tell me
you knew Elizabeth Plimpton?
(Leonard:)I am a huge fan of hers.
I didn't realize I had to share
my connection...
(Sheldon:)...with things you're a fan of,
but, very well.
(Sheldon:)You enjoy Canadian bacon.
I've been to Toronto.
-Okay, fine. Where is she gonna sleep?
-My room, of course.
(Raj:)Holy crap.
-Yeah, I have a two-part question.
-Go ahead.
(Howard:)A, are you kidding me?
(Howard:)And B, seriously,
are you freaking kidding me?